# BYUNGWOO JEON

imbw2024@kaist.ac.kr \leftharpootyjeon.github.io \leftharpootyjeon

#### RESEARCH INTEREST

The northstar of my research is finding a unified and scalable framework aligned with multi-modalities and human preferences for various vision tasks. To this end, I'm delving into robot learning focusing on building effective multi-modal representations of the 3D world to be used for real-world scenarios.

### • Multi-modal representation

- Alignment [P2]
- Hallucination

### • Robot learning

- Action modeling
- Imitation learning

# • High-dimensional vision

- Spatial understanding [P1, P2]
- Temporal understanding [C1]
- Motion estimation [C1]

### **PUBLICATIONS**

C: conference, J: journal, W: workshop, P: preprint / \* equal contribution

- [P2] SpatialBoost: Enhancing Visual Representation through Language-Guided Reasoning Byungwoo Jeon\*, Dongyoung Kim\*, Huiwon Jang, Insoo Kim, and Jinwoo Shin Under review
- [P1] Consistent Absolute Depth Estimation via Coordinated Feature Synthesis in 3D Space Subin Kim\*, Seong Hyeon Park\*, <u>Byungwoo Jeon</u>, Sihyun Yu, Kihyuk Sohn, and Jinwoo Shin Under review
- [C1] TrackIME: Enhanced Video Point Tracking via Instance Motion Estimation Seong Hyeon Park, Huiwon Jang, <u>Byungwoo Jeon</u>, Sukmin Yun, Paul Hongsuck Seo, and Jinwoo Shin Conference on Neural Information Processing Systems (NeurIPS), 2024, <u>Spotlight Presentation</u>

# WORK EXPERIENCE

ALINLAB, Research Intern (advisor: Prof. Jinwoo Shin)	Jeongja, South Korea / Mar 2023 - Aug 2024
Arcreal, ML Engineer (host: Prof. Jinwoo Shin)	Gangnam, South Korea / Jan 2023 - Jan 2024
MLVLAB, Research Intern (advisor: Prof. Hyunwoo J. Kim)	Anam, South Korea / Jul 2022 - Dec 2022
M-monstar, Fullstack Engineer	Pangyo, South Korea / Jul 2021 - Aug 2021

# **EDUCATION**

KAIST, M.S./Ph.D student in Artificial Intelligence (advisor: Prof. Jinwoo Shin)	Sep 2024 - Current
Korea University, B.S. in Computer Science and Engineering, Statistics	Mar 2020 - Aug 2024

### **EXTRACURRICULAR ACTIVITIES**

Google Developer Student Clubs @ Korea University, Lead and Founder Aug 2022 - Jul 2023

### HONORS & AWARDS

Silver Prize, K-Data Science Hackathon, 2023 (\$2,000) Top 8, Artificial Intelligence Grand Challenge, 2022 Dean's List, Korea University, 2020 - 2023

### **PROJECTS**

Google DSC, "Google Solution Challenge: Recovery," 2024

Google DSC, "Horang Studio: Diffusion-based personalized AI profile service," 2023

Google DSC, "Google Solution Challenge: digiHow," 2023

# SELECTED TALKS

Yonsei & Korea University, Google DSC, "Towards the New World of Computing: CV on Real-world," Dec 2024 Korea University, Google DSC, "Recent Advances in Machine Learning," Nov 2023

# **SKILLS**

- Language
  - Python Advanced
  - C/C++ Advanced
  - **Javasciprt** Intermediate
- ML/DL
  - **PyTorch** Advanced
  - TensorFlow Advanced